https://www.reonetwork.com/privacy.cfm

It's Fast, Easy and Free
Simply enter a complete address, or even just the city or ZIP code. REO Network will display local brokers, appraisers, attorneys, contractors, escrow and title companies, inspectors and more!
Search for REO Brokers, Agents and Vendors
Privacy Statement
REO Network® operates as a DBA of ClearCapital.com, Inc. ("Clear Capital"). Clear Capital:
(a) Collects non-public personal information about you from the following sources:
From applications or other forms we receive from you or your authorized representatives;
From transactions with, or from the services being performed by, us, our affiliates, or others;
From our internet web sites;
From the public records maintained by governmental entities; and
From consumer or other reporting agencies;
(b) Does not disclose any non-public personal information about you except:
to agents, independent contractors or representatives to provide you with requested services;
to third-party contractors or service providers who provide services or perform functions on our behalf;
to law enforcement or regulatory officials when applicable law or regulations require us to do so;
where required by law or judicial process (such as a court order);
to other parties with appropriate consent; or
otherwise to the extent permitted under federal or state privacy laws;
(c) Restricts access to non-public personal information to employees who need to know that information to provide services to clients; and
(d) Maintains physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to guard non-public personal information.
Use of REONetwork.com constitutes acceptance of this privacy policy and our terms of use.
Copyright 2000-2020 ClearCapital.com, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
Version 4.2008.09.16.
